moovly.com 2019-12-07

# Privacy Policy | Moovly

**Short**

Moovly located at Koning Albertlaan 114, B-9000 Gent is responsible for the processing of your Personal Data, via its website [https://www.moovly.com](https://www.moovly.com/).

Moovly processes data from the visitors and/or users for the following **purposes** :

  * Proper technical functioning and personalization of the Website;
  * Management of requests for information;
  * Conducting statistical research and analytics;
  * (Financial) reporting;
  * Performing payments and billing & debt collection;
  * Delivery of Moovly services, including without limitation, invoicing, customer relationship management;
  * Displaying content from external content providers;
  * Sending a newsletter and/or advertisement, or otherwise contact you about services or information we think may interest you and maintaining public relations
  * Supplier Management;
  * Investor Management;

You can always request **access** to – and **rectification** or **erasure** of Personal Data or to **restrict** the processing; as well as the right to **object** to processing, the right to data **portability** and the right to **withdraw** your consent at all times.

Personal Data are **transferred** to following recipients:

  * Processors that provide statistical research and analysis;
  * Processors who provide hosting of this Website and related databases;
  * Processors who provide could and other supported software services for business processing;
  * Processors that provide communication services;
  * Processors and controllers who act as a subcontractor for Moovly in the execution of the Services;
  * Processors and controllers who provide payment services;
  * Processors and controllers that act as agents or distributors of Moovly;
  * Companies associated with Moovly.

## 1 – Definitions

In this Privacy Statement the following terms are defined as follows:

  1. Moovly: Moovly NV, a company incorporated and existing under Belgian law, with its registered office at Koning Albertlaan 114, B-9000 Gent and registered with the Crossroads Bank for Enterprises under number 0500.669.260;
  2. Website: the website of Moovly, https://www.moovly.com, and derivative websites developed and administered by Moovly;
  3. Controller: means the natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which, alone or jointly with others, determines the purposes and means of the processing of personal;
  4. Processor: means a natural or legal person, public authority, agency or other body which processes personal data on behalf of the Controller;
  5. Personal Data: Any information relating to an identified or identifiable natural person.
  6. Processing: Any operation or set of operations which is performed on personal data or on sets of personal data, whether or not by automated means, such as collection, recording, organisation, structuring, storage, adaptation or alteration, retrieval, consultation, use, disclosure by transmission, dissemination or otherwise making available, alignment or combination, restriction, erasure or destruction;  

## 2- Processing of Personal Data

This Privacy Statement is applicable to all Processing activities undertaken by Moovly acting as a Controller, unless further transparency is provided, through e.g. disclaimers, electronic means or orally for and in as far as your data is subject to the Data Protection Legislation.

Moovly attaches great importance to respecting and protecting your privacy and the confidentiality and safety of your Personal Data. Your Personal Data is Processed in accordance with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 (hereinafter ‘GDPR’ or ‘Data Protection Legislation’).

For the purposes of this Privacy Policy Moovly acts as the Controller, meaning that it determines why (as detailed below in title 4 Purposes of processing) and how your Personal Data is Processed (e.g. by storing, using, transferring, etc. data via our IT systems).

In some cases Moovly might act as a Processor, meaning that it simply Processes Personal Data on behalf of another Controller. If your Personal Data is processed by Moovly as a Processor on behalf of such other Controller, please refer to the privacy policy of that Controller for more information. 

Moovly allows Controllers for which it acts as Processor to enter into a Data Processing Addendum if required by applicable Data Protection Legislation, [click here for more information.](https://www.moovly.com/gdpr/data-processing-addendum)

## 3- What information

Where the information is provided by the data subject itself via a form, the fields denoted with (*) are strictly necessary for the purposes of processing, if one or more of these fields are not completed the form will not be executed. Other fields can be completed to better facilitate the provision of services by Moovly, if these are not filled out there will be no adverse effects.

### Website Visitors

Moovly may Process following Personal Data via its Website, through including without limitation, the contact form and cookies:

  * Information about your PC or mobile device and your visits and use of the Website, including your IP address, operating system, browser type and geographical location;
  * Information that you provide by using the contact form or newsletter form, such as your first name, last name and email address;
  * Information that you provide by completing surveys;
  * Information about how you use our Website;
  * Any other information that you choose to provide, by any means.

### Customers/Users

Moovly may Process following Personal Data via its Website, or as otherwise provided during your use of the services and products of Moovly, including support provided by Moovly:

  * Identification data, such as your name, email and address;
  * Information about your PC or mobile device and your visits and use of the Website, including your IP address, operating system, browser type and geographical location;
  * Financial identification data, such as your account number;
  * Any other information that you provide in your profile;
  * Media usage;
  * Support requests and information;
  * Account and licensing information;
  * Image recordings;
  * Sound recordings;
  * Any other information that you choose to provide, by any means.

### Leads

Moovly may Process following Personal Data of leads that you have provided or that we have received from third parties:

  * Identification data, such as your name, email and address;

### Investors/Stakeholders

Moovly may Process following Personal Data via its Website, through including without limitation, the subscription form:

  * Identification data, such as your name, email and address;

### Contact persons

Moovly may process following Personal Data of business contacts of its suppliers, customers, prospects, etc.:

  * Personal contact information that is provided to us, such as your first name, last name, email address, telephone number, mobile number;

## 4- Purposes of processing

Moovly collects and processes Personal Data for one or multiple of following purposes:

Purposes | Legal basis  
---|---  
Proper technical functioning and personalization of the Website; | Consent/ Legitimate interests of Moovly (development)  
Management of requests for information; | Consent/Performance of an agreement  
Conducting statistical research and analytics; | Legitimate interests of Moovly (research)  
(Financial) reporting; | Legitimate interests of Moovly (corporate housekeeping)  
Performing payments and billing & debt collection; | Performance of an agreement  
Delivery of Moovly services, including without limitation, invoicing, customer relationship management; | Performance of an agreement/ Legitimate interests of Moovly (corporate housekeeping)/ Legal obligation  
Displaying content from external content providers; | Consent  
Sending a newsletter and/or advertisement, or otherwise contact you about services or information we think may interest you and maintaining public relations | Consent/ Legitimate interests of Moovly (marketing)  
Supplier Management; | Performance of a contract/ Legitimate interests of Moovly (business relations)  
Investor Management; | Consent  
  
If the Moovly wishes to use Personal Data for an incompatible new purpose Moovly will request your consent prior to this new use, unless such Processing is required by Union or national law.

When the Processing is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw consent at any time, without affecting the lawfulness of Processing based on consent before its withdrawal.

## 5- Transfers of Personal Data

Personal Data is only processed by Moovly for internal use for the above described purposes. We do not rent or sell your Personal Data to third parties for use for their own purposes.

Within Moovly the data is passed on only to employees on a ‘’need to know’ basis.

Moovly can make use of data processors to process your Personal Data. Data processors are natural or legal persons, public authorities, agencies or other bodies which process Personal Data on behalf of Moovly.

Moovly can transfer the Personal Data to following (categories of) recipients:

  * Processors that provide statistical research and analysis;
  * Processors who provide hosting of this Website and related databases;
  * Processors who provide could and other supported software services for business processing;
  * Processors that provide communication services;
  * Processors and controllers who act as a subcontractor for Moovly in the execution of the Services;
  * Processors and controllers who provide payment services;
  * Processors and controllers that act as agents or distributors of Moovly;
  * Companies associated with Moovly.

Personal Data may be processed by these recipients outside the European Economic Area, Moovly will make sure appropriate safeguards are implemented. You can obtain a copy of the measures upon written request.

Moovly may alter its corporate structure through including changing legal form, merger, acquisitions and sale of affiliates, in such transactions Personal Data will be passed on in accordance with this Privacy Statement and applicable data protection law.

## 6- Personal Data storage duration

The Personal Data are kept by Moovly, in any case during the duration of the relevant agreements and for a period equal to the statutory period of limitation thereafter. In addition, Personal Data is kept for as long as required by law and no longer than necessary for the processing purposes described above.

## 7- Your rights

You are entitled to request from us access to and rectification or erasure of Personal Data or restriction of processing or to object to processing as well as the right to data portability; For this purpose you should send your dated and signed request to Moovly, Koning Albertlaan 114, B-9000 Gent, enclosing a copy of your identity card, or you can contact Moovly via email at info@moovly.com and furnish your email with an electronic signature.

Within one month of the submission of the request, you will be informed of the follow-up given to it.

You have the right to withdraw your consent for a particular Processing activity at any time, without this affecting the lawfulness of the processing on the basis of the consent before its withdrawal. In case you have given your permission to receive newsletters and advertising, you can withdraw it by changing your account settings or using the “unsubscribe / unsubscribe” link in this communication.

Finally, you at all times have the right to submit a complaint to the supervisory authority.

No automated decision making, including profiling, is used in the Processing of your Personal Data.

## 8- Anonymous data

Moovly is permitted to collect non-personal and anonymous data when the Website is visited and to anonymize Personal Data. This data does not allow Moovly to identify an individual person and this data can be shared with third parties, including for statistical and commercial purposes.

## 9- Cookies

### **Use of Cookies**

Moovly web sites use “cookies” to enable you to sign in to our Services and to help personalize your online experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies contain information that can later be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. One of the primary purposes of cookies is to store your preferences and other information on your computer in order to save you time by eliminating the need to repeatedly enter the same information and to display your personalized content and appropriate advertising on your later visits to these sites. When you sign in to a site using your credentials, we store your unique ID number, and the time you signed in, in an encrypted cookie on your hard disk. This cookie allows you to move from page to page at the site without having to sign in again on each page. When you sign out, these cookies are deleted from your computer. We also use cookies to improve the sign in experience. For example, your e-mail address may be stored in a cookie that will remain on your computer after you sign out. This cookie allows your e-mail address to be pre-populated, so that you will only need to type your password the next time you sign in. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies.

### **The use by Moovly of Google Analytics cookies**

We collect standard internet log information and details of visitor behaviour patterns by using[ Google Analytics](https://www.google.com/analytics/web/) cookies. We do this to find out things such as the number of visitors to the various parts of the site. This information does not identify visitors or collect any personal details. We do not make any attempt to find out the identities of those visiting our websites. We will not associate any data gathered from this site with any personal information from any source. We will make it clear when we collect personal information and will explain what we intend to use it for.

To provide website visitors with more choice on how their data is collected by Google Analytics, Google have developed the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on. The add-on communicates with the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js) to indicate that information about the website visit should not be sent to Google Analytics. The Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on does not prevent information from being sent to the website itself or to other web analytics services.

### **Control of cookies**

Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other interactive features of Moovly sites and services that depend on cookies.

To find out more about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set and how to manage and delete them, visit[ www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) which includes information on how to manage your settings for the major browser providers.

## 10- Changes

Moovly reserves the right to continually update this Privacy Statement.

_This Privacy Statement was last updated: 2 July 2018. Version 1.0_

## 11- Miscellaneous

If any of the provisions of this Privacy Statement would be wholly or partially annulled by a binding decision, this shall have no effect whatsoever on the other provisions of this Privacy Statement. Moovly is entitled to modify or replace such a provision by another provision which, within legal limits, has the same effect.

The failure of Moovly to demand strict compliance with the provisions of this Privacy Statement shall not be construed as a waiver or rejection thereof.

## 12- Applicable law

By visiting the Website and thus expressly accepting this Privacy Statement and the conditions therein, you agree that any dispute or claim relating to this Privacy Statement and the processing of Personal Data shall be governed by Belgian law and the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of Gent (Belgium).

## 13- Contact

If you have any questions or comments regarding the policy concerning the processing of Personal Data after reading this Privacy Statement, please contact the contact person at the address Koning Albertlaan 114, B-9000 Gent or you can contact Moovly via email at info@moovly.com.

Please send requests for additional general information concerning the protection of personal privacy to the Belgian Data Protection Authority to the address, 25 Drukpersstraat, B-1000 Brussels telephone number: +32 (0)2 274 48 00 or via email at [contact@apd-gba.be](mailto:contact@apd-gba.be) ([www. dataprotectionauthority.be](http://www.privacycommission.be/)).
